<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.phone.calindori.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Calindori</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxCalindorixx</name>
  <summary>Calendar application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aplicació de calendari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Kalenderprogramm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aplicación de calendarios</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Application d'agenda</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Aplicativo de calendario</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Applicazione calendario</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Agendatoepassing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Aplikacja kalendarza</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Aplicação de calendário</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Kalenderprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма-календар</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCalendar applicationxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Calindori is a touch friendly calendar application. It has been designed for mobile devices but it can also run on desktop environments. Users of Calindori are able to check previous and future dates and manage tasks and events.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Calindori és una aplicació de calendari tàctil. Està dissenyada per als dispositius mòbils, però també es pot executar als entorns d'escriptori. El usuaris del Calindori poden revisar dates anteriors i futures i gestionar tasques i esdeveniments.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Calindori es una aplicación de calendarios táctil. Ha sido diseñada para dispositivos móviles, aunque también se puede ejecutar en entornos de escritorio. Los usuarios de Calindori pueden comprobar fechas anteriores y futuras, así como gestionar tareas y eventos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Calindori est une application d'agenda ergonomique pour les écrans tactiles. Elle a été conçue pour les appareils mobiles mais fonctionne également sur les environnements de bureau. Les utilisateurs de Calindori peuvent consulter les dates passées et futures et gérer les tâches et les évènements.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Calindori é un aplicativo de calendario optimizado para uso táctil. Deseñouse para dispositivos móbiles pero tamén pode usarse en ambientes de escritorio. Os usuarios de Calindori poden consultar datas pasadas e futuras e xestionar tarefas e eventos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Calindori è un'applicazione calendario amichevole. È stato progettato per i dispositivi mobili, ma può anche funzionare in ambienti desktop. Gli utenti di Calindori sono in grado di controllare date precedenti e future, e di gestire attività ed eventi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Calindori is een agendatoepassing vriendelijk voor aanraken. Het is ontworpen voor mobiele apparaten maar het kan ook in een bureaubladomgeving werken. Gebruikers van Calindori kunnen eerdere en toekomstige datums controleren en taken en afspraken beheren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Calindori jest aplikacją kalendarza przystosowaną do dotyku. Została stworzona dla urządzeń przenośnych, lecz można ją także uruchomić na komputerach stacjonarnych. Użytkownicy Calindori mogą  sprawdzać poprzednie i przyszłe daty oraz zarządzać zadaniami i wydarzeniami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Calindori é uma aplicação de calendário amigável para dispositivos tácteis. Foi desenhada para dispositivos móveis, mas também pode ser executada em computadores. Os utilizadores do Calindori poderão ver as datas anteriores e futuras, assim como gerir as tarefas e eventos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Calindori är ett pekvänligt kalenderprogram. Det har konstruerats för mobilenheter men kan också köra på skrivbordsmiljöer. Användare av Calindori kan kontrollera tidigare och framtida datum, samt hantera uppgifter och händelser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calindori — програма-календар для сенсорних інтерфейсів. Її розроблено для мобільних пристроїв, але нею можна користуватися на звичайних комп'ютерних робочих станціях. Користувачі Calindori можуть читати записи попередніх і майбутніх подій і керувати записами завдань і подій.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalindori is a touch friendly calendar application. It has been designed for mobile devices but it can also run on desktop environments. Users of Calindori are able to check previous and future dates and manage tasks and events.xx</p>
    <p>When executing the application for the first time, a new calendar file is created that follows the ical standard. Alternatively, users may create additional calendars or import existing ones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">En executar l'aplicació per primera vegada, es crea un fitxer nou de calendari que segueix l'estàndard «ical». Alternativament, els usuaris poden crear calendaris addicionals o importar-ne d'existents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Beim ersten Start der Anwendung wird ein neuer Kalender nach dem ICal-Standard erstellt. Alternativ können zusätzliche Kalender erstellt oder vorhandene Kalender importiert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Al ejecutar la aplicación por primera vez, se crea un nuevo archivo de calendario conforme al estándar ical. De forma alternativa, los usuarios pueden crear calendarios adicionales o importar otros existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Lors de sa première exécution, l'application crée un nouveau fichier agenda respectant la norme ical. Les utilisateurs peuvent également créer des agendas supplémentaires ou importer des agendas existants.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ao executar o aplicativo por vez primeira, créase un novo ficheiro de calendario que segue o estándar de iCal. De maneira alternativa, os usuarios poden crear calendarios adicionais ou importar calendarios existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Quando si esegue l'applicazione per la prima volta viene creato un nuovo file di calendario che segue lo standard ical. In alternativa, gli utenti possono creare dei calendari aggiuntivi, oppure importare quelli esistenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bij het de eeerste keer uitvoeren van de toepassing, wordt een nieuw agendabestand aangemaakt die de ical-standaard gebruikt. Alternatief kunnen gebruikers extra agenda's aanmaken of bestaande importeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Przy wykonywaniu aplikacji po raz pierwszy, tworzony jest plik nowego kalendarza, który przestrzega standardu ical. Alternatywnie, użytkownicy mogą stworzyć dodatkowe kalendarz lub zaimportować już istniejące.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Ao executar a aplicação pela primeira vez, será criado um ficheiro de calendário novo que segue a norma iCal. Em alternativa, os utilizadores poderão criar calendários adicionais ou importar existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">När programmet körs för första gången skapas en ny kalenderfil som följer ical-standarden. Som alternativ kan användare skapa ytterligare kalendrar eller importera befintliga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Під час першого запуску програма створить файл стандартного календаря у форматі ical. Крім того, користувач може створювати додаткові календарі або імпортувати вже створені.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWhen executing the application for the first time, a new calendar file is created that follows the ical standard. Alternatively, users may create additional calendars or import existing ones.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Axenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozkład zajęć</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Порядок денний</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAgendaxx</li>
      <li>Events</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Esdeveniments</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ereignisse</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Eventos</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Évènements</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Eventos</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Eventi</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Afspraken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wydarzenia</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Eventos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Händelser</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Події</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEventsxx</li>
      <li>Todos</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pendents</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aufgaben</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Listas de tareas</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Tâches</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Tarefas</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cose da fare</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Taken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zadania-do-zrobienia</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Itens Por-Fazer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Uppgifter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Завдання</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTodosxx</li>
      <li>Multiple calendars</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Calendaris múltiples</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mehrere Kalender</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Múltiples calendarios</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Agendas multiples</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Varios calendarios</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Calendari multipli</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Meerdere agenda's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wiele kalendarzy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Vários calendários</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flera kalendrar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Користування декількома календарями</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple calendarsxx</li>
      <li>Import calendar</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa calendaris</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kalender importieren</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importar calendario</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Importer un agenda</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Importar un calendario</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importa calendario</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Agenda importeren </li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Importowanie kalendarzy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar o calendário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera kalender</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортування календарів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport calendarxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/dkardarakos/calindori/issues</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calindori</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
